{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 15 + 1 + 0?",
      "options": [
        16,
        10,
        24,
        18
      ],
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 91 + 1 + 3?",
      "options": [
        89,
        97,
        85,
        95
      ],
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 77 + 2 + 5?",
      "options": [
        78,
        89,
        83,
        84
      ],
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 31 + 5 + 4?",
      "options": [
        44,
        40,
        35,
        36
      ],
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 73 + 1 + 3?",
      "options": [
        80,
        73,
        77,
        83
      ],
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 36 + 3 + 5?",
      "options": [
        37,
        44,
        42,
        43
      ],
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 67 + 0 + 1?",
      "options": [
        68,
        63,
        67,
        62
      ],
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 89 + 2 + 3?",
      "options": [
        88,
        85,
        87,
        94
      ],
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 51 + 2 + 4?",
      "options": [
        56,
        57,
        52,
        48
      ],
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 43 + 3 + 2?",
      "options": [
        48,
        41,
        46,
        51
      ],
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 48 + 2 + 0?",
      "options": [
        41,
        43,
        50,
        57
      ],
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 89 + 0 + 1?",
      "options": [
        98,
        95,
        90,
        99
      ],
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 22 + 2 + 1?",
      "options": [
        25,
        28,
        33,
        17
      ],
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 45 + 0 + 0?",
      "options": [
        35,
        45,
        39,
        36
      ],
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 31 + 1 + 2?",
      "options": [
        40,
        24,
        34,
        35
      ],
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 18 + 1 + 5?",
      "options": [
        31,
        33,
        24,
        17
      ],
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 57 + 2 + 2?",
      "options": [
        71,
        61,
        63,
        68
      ],
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 23 + 4 + 2?",
      "options": [
        30,
        20,
        39,
        29
      ],
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 75 + 2 + 4?",
      "options": [
        81,
        77,
        84,
        73
      ],
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 31 + 4 + 3?",
      "options": [
        33,
        36,
        38,
        35
      ],
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 33 + 4 + 0?",
      "options": [
        43,
        33,
        27,
        37
      ],
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 85 + 2 + 0?",
      "options": [
        80,
        96,
        87,
        93
      ],
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 21 + 4 + 3?",
      "options": [
        26,
        25,
        28,
        34
      ],
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 42 + 2 + 2?",
      "options": [
        39,
        54,
        37,
        46
      ],
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 17 + 3 + 3?",
      "options": [
        32,
        23,
        16,
        14
      ],
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 73 + 0 + 1?",
      "options": [
        82,
        66,
        74,
        73
      ],
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 68 + 2 + 3?",
      "options": [
        70,
        67,
        73,
        64
      ],
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 25 + 3 + 5?",
      "options": [
        30,
        36,
        40,
        33
      ],
      "answer": 33
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 83 + 0 + 5?",
      "options": [
        83,
        88,
        81,
        87
      ],
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 43 + 0 + 4?",
      "options": [
        45,
        52,
        57,
        47
      ],
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 89 + 1 + 0?",
      "options": [
        90,
        85,
        99,
        86
      ],
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 67 + 2 + 5?",
      "options": [
        72,
        69,
        76,
        74
      ],
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 64 + 5 + 3?",
      "options": [
        72,
        65,
        81,
        69
      ],
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 31 + 3 + 3?",
      "options": [
        36,
        41,
        37,
        27
      ],
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 42 + 2 + 3?",
      "options": [
        47,
        55,
        37,
        46
      ],
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 81 + 4 + 5?",
      "options": [
        97,
        98,
        90,
        80
      ],
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 85 + 4 + 2?",
      "options": [
        90,
        82,
        91,
        94
      ],
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 93 + 2 + 2?",
      "options": [
        99,
        95,
        90,
        97
      ],
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 80 + 4 + 2?",
      "options": [
        77,
        87,
        86,
        96
      ],
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 71 + 4 + 4?",
      "options": [
        85,
        89,
        79,
        72
      ],
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 43 + 1 + 1?",
      "options": [
        43,
        45,
        38,
        40
      ],
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 65 + 2 + 2?",
      "options": [
        78,
        66,
        74,
        69
      ],
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 23 + 2 + 4?",
      "options": [
        35,
        20,
        29,
        34
      ],
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 65 + 5 + 5?",
      "options": [
        79,
        77,
        67,
        75
      ],
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 11 + 5 + 2?",
      "options": [
        21,
        18,
        12,
        23
      ],
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 44 + 3 + 5?",
      "options": [
        43,
        54,
        52,
        59
      ],
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 21 + 1 + 5?",
      "options": [
        35,
        21,
        18,
        27
      ],
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 67 + 0 + 0?",
      "options": [
        76,
        67,
        71,
        70
      ],
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 87 + 1 + 1?",
      "options": [
        81,
        88,
        96,
        89
      ],
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "Level 5: What is 80 + 3 + 5?",
      "options": [
        88,
        94,
        91,
        85
      ],
      "answer": 88
    }
  ]
}